hello my name is Joe Darcy I'm an
你好，我叫乔·达西，我是
engineer in Oracle's Java platform team
Oracle Java平台团队的工程师
and I'll be speaking today about small
我今天将谈论小
language changes in jt9 first however we
首先在jt9中更改语言，但是我们
should mention that there was a very
应该提到，有一个非常
large language change made in JDK 9 as
在JDK 9中大语言更改为
part of modularity that his project
他的项目是模块化的一部分
jigsaw there's a new kind of source file
拼图里有一种新的源文件
a module info dot Java file that's used
使用的模块信息点Java文件
to declare dependencies between modules
声明模块之间的依赖关系
as well as to declare what packages a
以及声明什么包裹
module exports and other information
模块导出和其他信息
like that there's much more to be said
像这样还有更多的话要说
about modules and to learn more about
关于模块，并了解更多有关
modules I recommend you listen to the
我建议您听模块
modules and JDK 9 talk by my colleague
模块和我同事的JDK 9演讲
Alex Buckley for the smaller language
小语言的亚历克斯·巴克利（Alex Buckley）
changes made in JDK 9 they come in two
在JDK 9中所做的更改分为两部分
categories one is a set of planned
类别之一是一组计划的
refinements for project lambda from JDK
JDK对lambda项目的改进
8 and project coin from JDK 7 and the
8，并从JDK 7和
second set of changes involves making
第二组变更涉及
the deprecation facility more
淘汰设施更多
informative project coin and JDK 7 was a
内容丰富的项目代币，而JDK 7是
collection of half a dozen small
收集小六个
language changes and we made further
语言更改，我们做了进一步的改进
refinements to 3 of those in JDK 9
对JDK 9中的3的改进
diamond try earth's resources and Varg
钻石尝试地球的资源和瓦格
warnings the small language changes in
警告小语言更改
included those updates the coin as well
包括那些更新硬币
as two updates related to project lambda
作为与lambda项目相关的两个更新
from dedicate and will speak through
从奉献，并会讲
these in terms first safe are args on
这些首先是安全的
private instance methods you could write
您可以编写的私有实例方法
code like this for some time
这样的代码一段时间
even back in jdk 5 or 6 using the
甚至使用
utility method arrays dot as lists in a
实用程序方法将点数组作为列表
platform to we easily create in this
我们在此轻松创建的平台
case a list of list of strings however
情况下，但字符串列表
when you compile this code if you were
当您编译此代码时
diligent about your warning message
谨慎对待您的警告消息
messages you'd note a warning like this
您会注意到这样的警告的消息
warning unchecked generic array creation
警告未经检查的通用数组创建
for VAR x parameter so what's going on
对于VAR x参数，这是怎么回事
here this warning is actually mandated
这里实际上是强制发出此警告
by the java language specification
由Java语言规范
because it's possible something bad
因为这可能是坏事
could be happening that something bad is
可能发生的事情是坏事
called heat pollution and it's discussed
称为热污染，并进行了讨论
in detail in the specification however
在规范中有详细说明
when you call the platform array
当您调用平台阵列时
thoughtless method nothing bad actually
周到的方法实际上没有什么不好
happens in this case the platform method
在这种情况下发生平台方法
is not misbehaving so this error is
不是行为异常，因此此错误是
uninformative even though it's mandated
即使是强制性的，也没有信息
by the platform we didn't think that was
通过平台，我们认为那不是
a very good situation
很好的情况
so in project Coyne we created a
因此在Coyne项目中，我们创建了一个
facility to get rid of these
摆脱这些的设施
uninformative warning messages and that
无关紧要的警告消息
facility was the save our args
设施是节省我们的参数
annotation if a programmer applies the
注释，如果程序员应用
safe varargs annotation to of our org
我们组织的安全varargs注释
method it lets the compiler know that
它使编译器知道的方法
the programmer is asserting that the VAR
程序员声称VAR
arguments that does not misbehave that
不会有不当行为的论点
heat pollution does not occur and
不会发生热污染
because of that the compiler is
因此，编译器是
justified by the updated specification
由更新的规范证明
to not emit warning messages at the
在不发出警告消息
declaration site of the method and more
方法的声明站点等
importantly any of the call sites of the
重要的是，
method so now as of JDK 7 you don't get
方法，因此从JDK 7开始，您不会
warning messages calling arrays dot as
警告消息调用数组点为
list because the design of the
列出原因是因为
annotation facility annotations are only
注释工具注释仅
inherited on classes not interfaces or
继承于类而不是接口或
methods therefore the safe args
方法，因此安全参数
annotation can only be used on methods
注释只能在方法上使用
that cannot be overridden what are the
不能被覆盖的是什么
kinds of methods that can't be
各种不可能的方法
overridden we can't override final
覆盖我们不能覆盖最终
methods or static methods constructors
方法或静态方法的构造函数
also can't be overridden from the VM
也不能从VM覆盖
point of view constructors are just very
观点的建设者只是非常
special cons of static methods there's
静态方法的特殊缺点
another category of methods that can't
另一类方法
be overridden and those are private
被覆盖，那些是私有的
methods and we omitted those back in JDK
方法，我们在JDK中省略了这些方法
7 but now in jdk 9 we've gotten around
7，但现在在jdk 9中我们已经解决了
to adding them so we had a very small
添加它们，所以我们有一个很小的
update to the java language
更新为Java语言
specification to now also allow say far
现在的规格还允许说远
arcs on private methods next effectively
接下来有效地解决私有方法
final variables and tribes resources as
最终变量和部落资源为
a reminder with the tribe earth
部落世界的提醒
resources statement you have a try block
资源声明，您有一个try块
that manages your resource R in this
在此管理您的资源R
case and the compiler internally
情况和内部编译器
translates this into a class file
将此转换为类文件
roughly equivalent to this where there's
大致相当于这个
a finally block wrapping a try and in
尝试包装的最后一块
the finally block close gets called on
最终块关闭被调用
the resource as long as it's not null
资源，只要它不为空
now it's actually a little more
现在实际上更多了
complicated
复杂
this to give better exception handling
这样可以提供更好的异常处理
so in terms of full disclosure this is
因此，就全面披露而言，这是
what the full destroyed ring looks like
完全毁灭的戒指看起来像什么
we don't have to worry about this as
我们不必为此担心
programmers because the compiler takes
程序员，因为编译器需要
care of this for us
为我们照顾这个
so back in JDK 7 the requirement was the
所以在JDK 7中，要求是
resource to be managed by the try with
尝试管理的资源
resources statement had to be a fresh
资源声明必须是新鲜的
variable declared as part of the
宣告为
statement that wasn't the original
声明不是原始的
proposal originally you could use any
最初可以使用任何建议
expression that had the right type if it
如果类型正确的表达式
was the article is full interface type
是文章的完整界面类型
that had the closed methods that was
具有封闭的方法是
fine however we noticed there was a
很好，但是我们注意到有一个
problem with that proposal we see that
该建议存在问题，我们看到
here let's say you have your resource
假设您有资源
are initialized to a new resource you
被初始化为您的新资源
manage the variable R with you try our
尝试管理变量R
three sources statement and within the
三个来源声明，并在
block you make it point to something
阻止你使它指向某事
else now when you come to the end of the
现在，当你走到尽头
charters resources block which objects
包机资源阻止了哪些对象
should have its closed method call
应该有其关闭的方法调用
resource 1 or resource two we decide we
资源1或资源2我们决定
didn't want to have to solve this
不想解决这个问题
problem and the solution was to require
问题，解决方案是要求
a fresh final variable to be used with
与之一起使用的新的最终变量
the try over three sources statement
试用三源声明
however that was a little overly
但是那有点太过分了
restrictive because if the expression
限制性的，因为如果表达
was already a final or effectively final
已经是决赛或有效决赛
variable this problem wouldn't occur so
变量不会发生此问题，所以
in JDK 9 we've relaxed the rules so if
在JDK 9中，我们放宽了规则，因此如果
you already have a final or effectively
您已经有了最终决定权或有效决定权
final resource you don't have to clear
您不必清除的最终资源
new variable for it so instead of
新变量而不是
declaring the resource R 2 in this case
在这种情况下声明资源R 2
you can just reuse your existing
您可以重复使用现有的
resource variable our little
资源变数
simplification that gets rid of some
摆脱一些简化
unnecessary boilerplate in the code next
代码中不必要的样板
we'll talk about diamonds with anonymous
我们将谈论匿名的钻石
classes diamond uses type inference
钻石类使用类型推断
inside the compiler to allow programmers
在编译器内部以允许程序员
to avoid having the type explicit type
避免使用显式类型
parameters when calling constructors
调用构造函数时的参数
so back before diamond if you wanted to
所以如果你想的话，回到钻石之前
do something like initialize your list
做类似初始化列表的操作
of maps of strings to integers you'd say
字符串映射为整数你会说
call new ArrayList and you'd repeat
调用新的ArrayList，然后重复
those type arguments map strings and
这些类型参数映射字符串，并且
integers but you don't have to do that
整数，但您不必这样做
anymore now you can just say new
现在你可以说新话了
ArrayList
数组列表
less the greater-than and the compiler
小于大于和编译器
will infer the rest for you now this
现在将为您推断其余部分
language feature is very effective at
语言功能非常有效
removing the need for explicit type
消除了对显式类型的需求
arguments however there are some cases
争论但是有一些情况
you can't use it because of a bad
你不能因为坏而使用它
worst-case interaction between diamond
钻石之间最坏情况的相互作用
and anonymous classes you cannot use
和匿名类，您不能使用
those with each other the problem is
那些彼此的问题是
there are cases where type inference can
在某些情况下，类型推断可以
infer something called a non des notable
推断出某种非显着的东西
type that nan de notable type is outside
nan de显着类型在外部的类型
the type system we can use as
我们可以用作的类型系统
programmers and it cannot be represented
程序员，无法代表
in the class file that needs to be
在需要的类文件中
generated for the anonymous class
为匿名类生成
however that's a worst case outcome in
但是，这是最坏的情况
many cases a de notable type is inferred
在许多情况下，可以推断出显着的类型
and that could be represented in a class
这可以在一个班级中代表
file so we thought this restriction was
文件，所以我们认为此限制是
a bit unfortunate and we did note when
有点不幸，我们确实注意到
we were finishing up project coin in JDK
我们正在用JDK完成项目硬币
7 that in the future we might relax this
7将来我们可能会放松这一点
restriction and allow diamond and
限制并允许钻石和
anonymous classes to be used together as
匿名类一起使用
long as that worst-case outcome didn't
只要那个最坏的结果没有
occur and that is indeed what we've done
发生，这的确是我们所做的
now in JDK 9 we've loosened the
现在在JDK 9中我们放宽了
restriction and now you can use diamond
限制，现在您可以使用钻石
with anonymous classes in many cases in
在许多情况下使用匿名类
JDK 7 we found that diamond was very
在JDK 7中，我们发现钻石非常
effective at eliminating explicit type
有效消除显式类型
arguments over 90% of a constructor call
超过构造函数调用的90％的参数
sites and with this new enhancement we
网站，有了这项新的增强功能，我们
feel that allowing diamond with
觉得允许钻石与
anonymous classes allow removal of a
匿名类允许删除
large fraction of the remaining 10%
其余10％的很大一部分
we've had good experiences using this
我们在使用这个方面有很好的经验
feature in the JDK codebase and
JDK代码库中的功能
eliminated hundreds of additional call
消除了数百个额外的通话
sites the next two small language
网站接下来的两种小语言
changes are updates to the project
更改是对项目的更新
lambda features that were added in eight
在八个功能中添加的lambda功能
first underscore is no longer an
第一个下划线不再是
identifier name starting in 8 the
标识符名称从8开始
compiler issued warnings if you used
如果您使用过，编译器会发出警告
underscore as an identifier warning that
下划线作为标识符警告
it might be not be allowed in future
将来可能不允许
versions of the platform and indeed now
该平台的版本，甚至现在
in JT 9 it is not allowed and what was a
在JT 9中是不允许的，什么是
warning message is now an error so why
警告消息现在是错误，为什么
are we doing this we want to reclaim the
我们在这样做我们想回收
underscore as syntactic real-estate and
强调为语法房地产
repurpose it for more useful things
将其重新用于更多有用的东西
those more useful things are described
描述那些更有用的东西
in JEP 302 lambda leftovers JEP being a
在JEP 302 lambda剩菜JEP是
JDK enhancement proposal as part of land
JDK增强建议作为土地的一部分
in JDK 8 you could add methods to
在JDK 8中，您可以将方法添加到
interfaces that had code these are
有代码的接口是
called default methods so these methods
称为默认方法，所以这些方法
are non abstract and thus they have a
是非抽象的，因此它们有一个
method body at the VM level and JDK 8
VM级别和JDK 8的方法主体
interfaces could have private methods
接口可以具有私有方法
and these were used to help implement
这些被用来帮助实施
the lambdas and so forth however at the
lambda等，但是在
source level programmers could not
源代码级程序员无法
declare a private interface methods in
在中声明私有接口方法
JDK 8 and now we can in JDK 9 you can
JDK 8，现在我们可以在JDK 9中
declare both private static methods as
将两个私有静态方法都声明为
well as private instance methods how
以及私有实例方法如何
would you use such a private method on
你会在这样的私人方法
an interface you can use them as helper
可以将它们用作帮助程序的界面
message to implement the other public
实施其他公众的信息
default methods and we've found this
默认方法，我们已经找到了
feature to be very useful in writing the
该功能在编写
JDK the next two small changes are both
JDK接下来的两个小改动都是
related to the deprecation facility
与折旧设施有关
first we'll talk about deprecation
首先，我们将讨论弃用
warnings and imports one of the ways
警告和导入的方法之一
we've paid down the technical debt in
我们已经偿还了
the JDK is to reduce the number of
JDK是为了减少
warnings in our code base we've actually
在我们的代码库中，警告实际上
cleared of all categories of warnings in
清除了所有类别的警告
large fractions to code and that has
要编码的大部分
included eliminating the deprecation
包括消除折旧
warnings now when do you get deprecation
现在警告您何时弃用
warnings these are discussed in the java
这些警告将在Java中讨论
language specification and you get them
语言规范，您就会得到
when you use a deprecated type method
当您使用不推荐使用的类型方法时
constructor and so forth and there's
构造函数等等，还有
three ways you can resolve those
解决这些问题的三种方法
warnings you can stop using the
警告，您可以停止使用
deprecated elements that's preferred
首选的不推荐使用的元素
when you can do it what you can't always
当你能做到的时候
do it you can propagate the deprecated
做到这一点，您可以传播不赞成使用的内容
annotation to the use sites now that's
现在是使用站点的注释
worse than the disease because you're
比疾病更糟糕，因为你
expanding rather than contracting the
扩大而不是缩小
number of deprecated elements and
不推荐使用的元素数量，以及
finally you can use the suppress
最后你可以使用抑制
warnings annotation to let the compiler
警告注释让编译器
know that you don't want to get this
知道你不想得到这个
warning message anymore so let's say you
警告消息了，所以再说一遍
have your client library and you're
有您的客户库，而您
using a deprecated library and you you
使用不推荐使用的库，您
want to suppress the warnings from the
想要抑制来自
annotations because you get the warning
注释，因为您收到警告
message here and you want to get rid of
消息在这里，你想摆脱
that
那
you might think alright right at the top
您可能会认为在顶部正确
of the class I'll suppress the
在班上我会压制
deprecation warnings and I won't have to
弃用警告，而我不必
do anything else however when you
但是当你做其他的事情
compile this code you find you still get
编译此代码，您仍然会得到
the deprecation warning so what's going
弃用警告，这是怎么回事
on here well if you look at the warning
如果你看警告的话
message in more detail the warning isn't
更详细的消息警告不是
from the body of the code in the class
从类中的代码主体
it's actually from the import statement
实际上是从import语句
instead right at the top of the file now
现在就在文件顶部
this import is mandated by the Java
此导入由Java强制执行
language specification and worse you
语言规范，使您更糟
can't use the suppress warnings
不能使用抑制警告
annotations on the import statement is
import语句上的注释是
not syntactically allowed so this
在语法上不允许这样做
warning is pretty unhelpful if all the
如果所有的警告都无济于事
other uses of the deprecated type can be
不推荐使用的类型的其他用途可以是
suppressed
压抑
why can't you eliminate the warning from
你为什么不能消除警告
the import statement that doesn't seem
似乎没有的导入语句
very helpful and indeed we change this
非常有帮助，的确，我们对此进行了更改
behavior in JDK 9 by not requiring a
JDK 9中的行为不需要
warning message in that location anymore
该位置不再显示警告消息
and because of this it's now tractable
正因为如此，它现在很容易处理
to clear a large code base at
清除大型代码库
deprecation warnings and we have an
弃用警告，我们有一个
existence proof of that from the JDK
JDK的存在证明
both the Java based module and Java
基于Java的模块和Java
desktop modules have been cleared of
桌面模块已清除
deprecation warnings
弃用警告
what does deprecation means it's a
弃用是什么意思
facility that's been in the platform for
平台中已经存在的设施
a long time but there's been some
很长一段时间，但有一些
uncertainty about the semantics of it if
如果它的语义不确定
something deprecated because it's
之所以弃用，是因为
harmful or is it deprecated because it's
是有害的，还是因为它
going away and if it's deprecated
走开，如果它已被弃用
because it's going away
因为它要消失了
why haven't more items been removed from
为什么还没有从中删除更多项目
the JDK over the years we've made some
这些年来，JDK已经做了一些
progress removing removing deprecated
进度删除删除不推荐使用
items in JDK 9 but we also thought more
JDK 9中的项目，但我们也想到了更多
information you needed to be conveyed in
您需要传达的信息
the deprecation annotation to
弃用注释
distinguish between these different
区分这些不同
cases and we did that by adding a new
案例，我们通过添加一个新的案例
method to the deprecation annotation for
弃用注释的方法
removal method that was either true or
删除方法为true或
false it defaults to false however if
false，默认为false，但是如果
it's marked as true that's an indication
标记为true表示
to you as a developer that you should
作为开发人员，您应该
migrate away from using that because it
不再使用它，因为它
will be removed in some future release
在将来的版本中将被删除
of the platform the tooling around
平台周围的工具
deprecation was operated to handle this
进行了弃用处理
about both the language specification
关于两种语言规范
as well as Java C and Java to talk all
以及Java C和Java可以说全部
had updates to handle this and there's a
有更新来处理此问题，并且有一个
new static analysis analysis tool in the
新的静态分析工具
JDK J deeper scan that analyzes class
分析类的JDK J更深层扫描
files and jar files for uses of api's
api的文件和jar文件
that are deprecated in the jdk to give
在jdk中弃用的
you additional warning that your
您另外警告您
application might be using them so you
应用程序可能正在使用它们，所以您
can take some action to stop using them
可以采取一些措施停止使用它们
so in conclusion modularity is the large
所以总的来说，模块化是很大的
language change coming in jdk 9 but
语言更改即将在jdk 9中发布，但
there are many other useful updates we
我们还有许多其他有用的更新
went through doing plan language
经历过计划语言
improvements to the language changes
语言变化的改进
previously made in JDK seven and eight
以前用JDK 7和8制作
these are great very straightforward to
这些是非常非常直接的
use and you can use them in your own
使用，您可以自己使用它们
code today and to start using them in
今天的代码，并开始在其中使用
your new code you can download a version
您的新代码，您可以下载一个版本
of the JDK for your platform if you're
适用于您平台的JDK
interested in getting involved in the
有兴趣参与
development to open JDK you can look at
开JDK开发你可以看一下
the mailing lists on the open JDK
打开的JDK上的邮件列表
website and you can also get updates on
网站，您还可以获取有关的更新
open JDK by following open JDK on
通过在以下位置打开JDK来打开JDK
Twitter thank you
Twitter谢谢